one another video. So let me explain another one of the technique to dump an L says. So this
will not be happening commonly, but you need to little bit care about this. So sometime
the threat factor will be compromising the RDP or remote stop connections. If the threat
factor has a remote stop connection or any of remote services, the threat factor is using.
So that time they can be able to control your desktop by by this. They can see the screen
they can be able to open any process without having any without any keyboard inputs. Okay.
They can they can they can open a task manager and they can open it and they can perform
the dump. Okay. Basically, right. So if they are entered in RDP connection. So that
time, we need to take little care about that. Okay. So if you want to dump L says here,
we can see an L says if you if they want to dump, they will be easily they will be opening
the task manager and they'll be creating a dump. Okay. So the dump will be created. See
user update a local, uh, let me redirect to this directory. Let's check, uh, yeah. So if you
see here, there is a L says dump that has been, uh, sitting and it will be created or to
1825 to 50, right. So this is one of the easiest techniques that will be followed by the
threat factor, but when you while you were investigating, so you'll be like, uh, it will be done
by the user. So so sometime the threat factors will be taking the RDP connection remote
section and they will be dumping, uh, it normally, right. Okay. So we'll be little care
about that. Okay. Okay. Guys, let's school, um, let's swap off and we'll connect in next
video. Bye. Bye.